<resources>

    <string name="desciption"><pre> <b>Punjab </b> or <b>panjab</b> is a state in  northern India. Punjab region
     is borderedby the Indian states of Jammu and Kashmir to the north,Himachal Pradesh to</pre> the east,Haryana to the south and
     southeast, Rajasthan to th southwest, and the  Pakistan province of Punjab to the west. It is the twentieth largest
     Indian state by area. With 27,704,236 inhabitants at the 2011 census, Punjab is the sixteenth largest state by population,
     comprising 22 districts.The Language Punjabi,is the most widely spoken and
     official language of the state. The main ethnic group are the Punjabis,  with Punjabi Sikhs (57.7 percent) forming  the
     demographic majority followed by Hindus (38.5 percent). The
     state capital is located in Chandigarh, a Union Territory and
     also the capital of the Haryana(neighboring state).\n\n </string>
    <string name="politics">Punjab is governed through a parliamentary system of representative democracy. Each of the
        states of India possesses a parliamentary system of government, with aceremonial state Governor, appointed by
        the President of India on the advice of thecentral government. The head of government is an indirectly elected
        Chief Minister whois vested with most of the executive powers. The term length of the government isfive years.
        The state legislature, the Vidhan Sabha, is the unicameral PunjabLegislative Assembly, with 117 members elected
        from single-seat constituencies. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="description">Primary and Secondary education is mainly affiliated to Punjab School Education Board.
 Punjab is served by several institutions of higher education, including 23 universities that
 provide undergraduate and postgraduate courses in all the major arts, humanities, science, engineering,
 law, medicine, veterinary science, and business. Punjab Agricultural University is a leading
 institution globally for the study of agriculture and played a significant role in Punjab Green
 Revolution in the 1960s–70s. Alumni of the Panjab University, Chandigarh include Manmohan Singh, the
 former Prime Minister of India, and Dr. Har Gobind Khorana, a biochemistry nobel laureate.
One of the oldest institutions of medical education is the Christian Medical College,
 Ludhiana, which has existed since 1894.[50] There is an existing gap in education between
 men and women, particularly in rural areas of Punjab. Of a total of 1 million 300 thousand
 students enrolled in grades five to eight, only 44% are women.
Punjab has 23 universities, of which 10 are private, 9 are state,
1 is central and 3 are deemed universities. Punjab has 1.04 lakh (104,000) engineering seats.</string>
    <string name="description1">
        The plain area  in the state of Punjab do not have any thick forests, the only available patches are of grass, small bush and shrubs.
        In the southern east part of state of Punjab and the areas of Hoshiarpur and Multan, the delicious mango fruit is grown.
        The other varieties of fruits that are grown in abundance here are orange, apple, fig, quince, almond, pomegranate, peach,
        mulberry, apricot and plum. The region that has major cultivation of rich flora and fauna can be majorly seen in the Shivalik
        ranges in the state of Punjab. Due to rich flora and fauna in the Shivalik region, it has been also termed as the zone
        of micro-endemic in India.\n\n The variety of angiosperms in the area includes 355 different types of herbs, trees of 70 different
        types; shrubs all in big and small sizes are of 70 different kinds, climbers of 19 different types can also be seen while 21
        different types of twines can also be seen here. Other than angiosperms, other varieties available are 31 kinds of pteridophytes,
        bryophytes of 27 different kinds while a special species of gymnosperms named as Pinus Roxburghii can be seen in the ranges
        in state of Punjab. The fauna of the area is also rich that has birds of 396 different types, Lepidoptera is of 214 different
        kinds, 55 varieties of fish species can also be seen, reptiles of 20 different types are also available and mammals of 19
        different kinds can be seen in these ranges. The state of Punjab is adored with large wetland area, number of bird sanctuaries
        that houses different varieties of numerous species of birds and a large number of zoological parks. Few of them to be named
        are wetland named as National wetland Hari-Ke-Pattan, the wetland of Kanjli, the wetlands of Kapurthala Sutlej, the number
        of wildlife sanctuaries include the Harika wildlife in district of Tarn Taran Sahib, Zoological Park in Ropar, Chhatbir Bansar
        Garden located in Sangrur Aam Khas Bagh
        situated in Sirhind, Amritsar’s famous Ram Bagh, Shalimar Garden in Kapurthala and the famous Baradari Garden in city of Patiala.\n
    </string>
    <string name="celebraties1">Primary and Secondary education is mainly affiliated to Punjab School Education Board.
 Punjab is served by several institutions of higher education, including 23 universities that
 provide undergraduate and postgraduate courses in all the major arts, humanities, science, engineering,
 law, medicine, veterinary science, and business. Punjab Agricultural University is a leading
 institution globally for the study of agriculture and played a significant role in Punjab Green
 Revolution in the 1960s–70s. Alumni of the Panjab University, Chandigarh include Manmohan Singh, the
 former Prime Minister of India, and Dr. Har Gobind Khorana, a biochemistry nobel laureate.
One of the oldest institutions of medical education is the Christian Medical College,
 Ludhiana, which has existed since 1894.[50] There is an existing gap in education between
 men and women, particularly in rural areas of Punjab. Of a total of 1 million 300 thousand
 students enrolled in grades five to eight, only 44% are women.</string>
    <string name="culture1">Primary and Secondary education is mainly affiliated to Punjab School Education Board.
 Punjab is served by several institutions of higher education, including 23 universities that
 provide undergraduate and postgraduate courses in all the major arts, humanities, science, engineering,
 law, medicine, veterinary science, and business. Punjab Agricultural University is a leading
 institution globally for the study of agriculture and played a significant role in Punjab Green
 Revolution in the 1960s–70s. Alumni of the Panjab University, Chandigarh include Manmohan Singh, the
 former Prime Minister of India, and Dr. Har Gobind Khorana, a biochemistry nobel laureate.
One of the oldest institutions of medical education is the Christian Medical College,
 Ludhiana, which has existed since 1894.[50] There is an existing gap in education between
 men and women, particularly in rural areas of Punjab. Of a total of 1 million 300 thousand</string>
    <string name="sports1"> Punjabis play a wide variety of sports and games, ranging from modern games such as hockey and cricket, to the
        more traditional games such as Kabaddi, Kushtian (wrestling) and Khuddo khoondi (similar to hockey). There are over 100
        traditional games and sports of Punjab
    To promote traditional games of Punjab, the state government has since 2014 been working on initiatives to promote the Punjab Rural Games.
        The games will include sports such as Kushtian in the state.\n
    </string>
    <string name="geo1"> <b> \tArea-</b>\t\t\t\t \t\t\t\t\t50,362 sq km \n
        <b>Location-</b>\t\t\t\t\ Northwest of India\n

        <b> Latitude-</b>\t\t\t\t\t  29"30’N - 32"32’N \n

        <b>Longitude-</b>\t\t\t
73"55’E - 76"50’E\n\n
        Located in the fertile great North Indian Plain, the state of Punjab has a combined area of 50,362 kmsq.
        The state shares its borders with Pakistan on the west, on its northern frontier by the Jammu and Kashmir,
        Himachal Pradesh on the east while the south is bordered by Rajasthan and Haryana.
The major area of Punjab falls in the belt of the great north Indian fertile land with an abundance of Alluvial Soil
        which is irrigated by a wonderful system of rivers and manmade canals. To add to this, a string of mountains
        strengthen the land. On an average, the height of these is almost 300 meters above sea level. On the southern part,
        the state and its
        soil becomes semi arid, which gives way to the Thar. The Shivalik also run along the state and form as the foothills of
        the great Himalayas.\n\n
        Punjab’s climate is characterized by extreme hot and extreme cold conditions. Annual temperatures in Punjab vary from one °C to forty six °C (min/max),
        however will reach forty nine °C in summer and zero °C in winter. The northeast space lying close to the foothills of the chain receives significant rain,
        whereas the realm lying any south and west receives
        less rain and experiences higher temperatures. Average annual rain ranges between 960 millimeter within the sub mountain region and 460 millimeter within the plains.
        \n\n
        <b>Climate:\n</b>
        The climatic conditions of Punjab are identified as an extreme of both the summers and the winters. On an average, the temperature
        in the state of Punjab varies from -4 degrees and goes up to 49 degrees which explains the extremeness of its climate.
        The places that are close to the Himalayan ranges are often penetrated by heavy rainfall, while the southern parts of the
        state are high on temperature and considerably low on rainfall.\n\n
        <b>Major Seasons of Punjab: \n</b>
        1. Summer (From April to June): In this season, temperature typically rises as high as 100 Fahrenheit.\n\n
        2.Monsoon (From July to September): this is the time when the majority of rainfall occurs.\n\n
        3.Winter (From December to February): this is the time when temperatures typically fall as low as 0 °C.\n\n\n








    </string>
    <string name="flora1">
        The plains in the state of Punjab do not have any thick forests, the only available patches are of grass, small bush
        and shrubs. In the southern east part of state of Punjab and the areas of Hoshiarpur and Multan, the delicious mango
        fruit is grown. The other varieties of fruits that are grown in abundance here are orange, apple, fig, quince, almond,
        pomegranate, peach, mulberry, apricot and plum. The region that has major cultivation of rich flora and fauna can be
        majorly seen in the Shivalik ranges in the state of Punjab. Due to rich flora and fauna in the Shivalik region, it has
        been also termed as the zone of micro-endemic in India. The variety of angiosperms in the area includes 355 different
        types of herbs, trees of 70 different types; shrubs all in big and small sizes are of 70 different kinds, climbers of
        19 different types can also be seen while 21 different types of twines can also be seen here. Other than angiosperms,
        other varieties available are 31 kinds of pteridophytes, bryophytes of 27 different kinds while a special species of
        gymnosperms named as Pinus Roxburghii can be seen in the ranges in state of Punjab. The fauna of the area is also rich
        that has birds of 396 different types, Lepidoptera is of 214 different kinds, 55 varieties of fish species can also be
        seen, reptiles of 20 different types are also available and mammals of 19 different kinds can be seen in these ranges.
        The state of Punjab is adored with large wetland area, number of bird sanctuaries that houses different varieties of numerous
        species of birds and a large number of zoological parks. Few of them to be named are wetland named as National wetland
        Hari-Ke-Pattan, the wetland of Kanjli, the wetlands of Kapurthala Sutlej, the number of wildlife sanctuaries include the Harika
        wildlife in district of Tarn Taran Sahib, Zoological Park in Ropar, Chhatbir Bansar Garden located in Sangrur Aam Khas
        Bagh situated in Sirhind, Amritsar’s famous Ram Bagh, Shalimar Garden in Kapurthala and the famous Baradari Garden in
        city of Patiala.\n\n
        <b> Plants:</b>\n


        A variety of flora, which includes aquatic as well as terrestrial plants are also found here, and the important ones are
        Hydrilla, Typha, Phragmites, Ficus, Prosopis, Azolla, Dalbergia, Ipomoea aquatic, Zizyphus Mauritiana, Albizzia, Syzgium
        cumini, Grasses, Nelumbo and Cyprus.\n\n
        <b>Common plants Found in Punjab: \n</b>
        1.Pipal \n
        2.Borh \n
        3.Siris \n
        4.Vilyati kikar \n
        5.Lasura \n
        6.Sohanjana\n
        7.Dhrek\n
        8.Ber \n
        9.Jaman \n\n








    </string>
    <string name="wadali1">The Wadali Brothers – Puranchand Wadali and Pyarelal Wadali – are Sufi singers and musicians from
     Guru Ki Wadali in the Amritsar District in Punjab, India. Born into the fifth generation of musicians given to singing the messages
     of Sufi saints, the Wadali brothers dabbled in the most unexpected of professions before they became Sufi singers. While Puranchand Wadali
     , the elder brother, was a regular in an akhara (English: wrestling ring) for 25 years,
     Pyarelal contributed to the meager family income by playing the role of Krishna in the village rasleela.
    Their father, Thakur Das Wadali, compelled Puranchand into music. Puranchand studied music from celebrated masters like Pandit Durga Das
     and UstadBade Ghulam Ali Khan of the Patiala Gharana. Pyarelal was trained by his elder brother, whom he considers his mentor and guru
     even today.\n\n
    They live in their ancestral house in Guru Ki Wadali, and teach music to those who promise to preserve it. They do not charge their
        disciples, and lead a very simple life devoted to the divine one. They believe
        in the Sufi tradition deeply. They consider themselves as a medium through which the preaching of great saints is passed on to others.\n\n

        In 2003, they stepped into the world of Bollywood music, rendering music director and writer
        Gulzar's soulful lyrics in their unique style in the film Pinjar, Dhoop, Tanu weds Manu, Mausam.\n\n

        <b>Awards: \n</b>
        1.Sangeet Natak Akademi Award, 1992.\n
        2.Tulsi Award, 1998.\n
        3. Punjab Sangeet Natak Akademi Award, 2003.\n
        4.Puranchand Wadali was awarded the Padma Shri award by the Government of India, 2005.\n
        5.Life Time Achievement Award 2015 in PTC awards in jalandhar.\n


    </string>
    <string name="yuvi1">Yuvraj Singh is an Indian international cricketer,
        who plays all forms of the game. An all-rounder who bats left-handed in the middle
  order and bowls slow left-arm orthodox, Yuvraj is the son of former Indian fast bowler and Punjabi actor Yograj Singh.
  Yuvraj has been a member of the Indian cricket team in ODIs since October 2000 and played his first Test match in October 2003.
  He was the vice-captain of the Indian ODI team between 2007–2008. He was the Man of the Tournament in the 2011 ICC Cricket World Cup,
  and one of the top performers at the 2007 ICC World Twenty20, both of which India won. In a match against England at the 2007 World Twenty20,
  he famously hit six sixes in one over bowled by Stuart Broad — a feat performed only three times previously in any form of senior cricket,
  and never in an international match between two Test cricket teams. In the same match, he set the record for the fastest fifty in Twenty20
  Internationals and in all Twenty20 cricket, reaching 50 runs in 12 balls.
  During the 2011 World Cup, he became the first player to take a 5-wicket haul and score a 50 in the same World Cup match.\n\n
    <b>Yuvraj Singh early Life History:\n</b>
Yuvraj Singh was born on 12 December, 1981 in a punjabi family. His favorite games during childhood were tennis and roller staking.
        Yuvraj was advice by his father to throw away playing these games and keep his full concentration of cricket.
        That was the best advice which make Yuvi such a fantastic player of the game. Yuvi made his first International appearance
        against Kenya where he got four overs to bowl. He conceded 16 runs and did not manage to get a chance to bat. The quarter game
        against Australia was special for him. While playing against pace attack of Glenn McGrath, Brett Lee, Yuvraj scored 84 runs of
        just 80 balls. This performance make him man of the match which is one of the best life achievement in his life history.
        In 2001, Yuvraj scored 98 runs against Sri-lanka in the fifth ODI match.
        Although he did not perform well in rest of the matches yet he showed some good pace with bowling by registering 8 wickets.\n\n
        In 2002 Natwest series against Sri-lanka and England, Yuvraj singh got man of the match award for his all round performance.
        He scored 64 runs and got 3 wickets for 39 runs. His unbeatable 64 helped India to chase down the total of 271. In another game,
        Yuvi scored 40 of just 19 balls but that match was white washed due to rain. In a game against Sri-lanka, Yuvraj played some
        good knock to drag his team for 59-4 in order to accomplish the target of 188 along with Dravid.
        In final, England has put a big total of 325 on the board. India were 146-5 when Yuvraj Singh along with Kaif started
        bringing the team towards the target. They shared a partnership of 121 runs.
        Yuvi was dismissed for 63 runs. At the end, India had won the game and that was a big achievements for Yuvraj too.\n\n
        <b>Records and Achievements  \n</b>
        1.Yuvraj Singh has got 3 Tests centuries. All these centuries came against Pakistan. In all these cases, either India lost or match resulted in drawn.\n
        2. Yuvraj has got 13 ODI centuries. The first one came was in 2003 against Bangaldesh. Last time he scored century was against West-Indies in 2011.\n
        3.Yuvraj Singh has hit <b>6 sixes</b> to Stuart Broad in ICC T20 world cup 2007.\n
         4.He is the first all rounder who has got 15 wickets and 300 runs in a world cup.\n
        5.He has been awarded with<b> Arjuna award</b>.\n
        6.He was awarded with<b> Padma Shri award in 2014</b>. That is a big life achievement for him.\n






    </string>
    <string name="amrish1">Amrish puri was an Indian actor, who was an important figure in Indian theatre and cinema. He worked with notable
  playwrights of the time, such as Satyadev Dubey and Girish Karnad. He is remembered for playing iconic negative roles in Hindi cinema
  as well as other Indian and international film industries. To Indian audiences he is the most remembered for his role as Mogambo in Shekhar
  Kapur\'\s Hindi film Mr. India (1987), and to Western audiences he is best known as Mola Ram in Steven Spielberg
  Hollywood film Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom (1984). Puri has won three Filmfare Awards for Best Supporting Actor.\n\n

 Amrish Puri acted in more than 400 films between 1967 and 2005, and was one of the most successful villains in Bollywood. 
  Puri first came to Mumbai following the footsteps of his elder brothers- Madan Puri and Chaman Puri, who were already 
  established actors known for playing villainous roles. He failed his first screen test, and instead found a job with the Employees 
  State Insurance Corporation Ministry of Labour and Employment (ESIC). \n\n
        At the same time, he started performing at the Prithvi Theatre in
  plays written by Satyadev Dubey. He eventually became well known as a stage actor and won the Sangeet Natak Akademi Award in 1979.[4]
  This theatre recognition soon led to work in television ads and eventually to films at the relatively late age of 40.
  Puri went on to work in Hindi, Kannada, Marathi, Hollywood, Punjabi, Malayalam, Telugu and Tamil films. Though he was successful in many 
  regional films, he is best known for his work in Bollywood cinema.\n\n
        <b>Awards: \n</b>
        1.1968, Maharashtra State Drama Competition.\n
        2.1979, Sangeet Natak Akademi Award for Theatre.\n
        3.1986, Filmfare Best Supporting Actor Award, Meri Jung.\n
        4.1991, Maharashtra State Gaurav Puraskar.\n
        5.1994, Sydney Film Festival, Best Actor Award – Suraj Ka Satvan Ghoda.\n
        6.1994, Singapore Film Festival, Best Actor Award – Suraj Ka Satvan Ghoda.\n
        7.1997, Filmfare Best Supporting Actor Award, Ghatak.\n
        8.1997, Star Screen Award Best Supporting Actor, Ghatak.\n
        9.1998, Filmfare Best Supporting Actor Award, Virasat.\n
        10.1998, Star Screen Award Best Supporting Actor, Virasat.\n\n

        <b>Death: \n</b>
        On 6 January 2017, Puri died at the age of 66, after having a heart attack at his residence in Andheri, Mumbai.
        He was honoured at the 89th Academy Awards in memoriam segment for his contribution in Indian and world cinema.
        \n\n
 
 </string>
    <string name="gurdas1">
            Gurdas Maan (Punjabi: ਗੁਰਦਾਸ ਮਾਨ, gurdās mān) is a Punjabi singer, songwriter, choreographer, and actor. He was born on January 4,
            1957 in Giddarbaha, Muktsar, Punjab, India. He gained national attention in India in 1980 with the song Dil Da Mamala Hai.
            Since then he has gone on to record over 27 albums and has written over 200 songs.
            Gurdas Maan is a legendary Punjabi singer and is considered as the heart of Punjab. His top hits have given him worldwide admiration.\n\n
        The legendary Gurdas Maan is today one of the most popular Punjabi alive. This bright shining star of Punjabi music and films has held the
        top spot hostage for nearly two decades. He has maintained an unprecedented universal appeal and won the heart of many global audiences.
        His style is unique and deviates from that of the many singers around with his extraordinary blend of vocal prowess and charisma that glows
        in his stage presence.\n\nThis is the man who started singing as a hobby and never thought he was good enough to become a professional
        singer until he started winning competitions at college. Since then he has exerted some kind of tidal pull over his
        audiences. He is one of those rare individuals who hypnotizes you with his persona and his power of speech.
        This college lecturer who holds a Masters degree in Physical Education and a black belt in Judo exploded into the music world in
        1982 with his first recording 'Dil Da Mamla' and turned the success of this album into a fruitful film career.
       Gurdas Mann has practically held the franchise for the promotion of Punjabi values through his elocutionary prowess and poignantly
        rich songs. His 'Apna Punjab Hove' has become a veritable anthem for Punjabi people throughout the world, and he extends his
        unique talent to respectfully kick start this album.\n\n<b> Early Life \n</b>
        Gurdas Maan was born in a Maan family in Gidderbaha Muktsar, Punjab (India). Gurdas Maan was formally educated in Malout.
        After completing his education there, his parents enrolled him into a further education institute in Patiala. As a keen sports
        enthusiast Gurdas was fascinated by the National Institute of Sports in the city, this prompted him to join the N.I.S and gain a Masters Degree in Physical Education.\n
        He took part in youth festivals organized by various universities and won several awards for his singing and acting, always supported
        by his friends. He competed in many athletic events and won medals including a bronze at the National Championship as well as achieving a black belt in judo.\n\n
        <b>Films \n</b> Gurdas Maan is best known as an actor for his remarkable performances in two films: Waris Shah: Ishq da Waris (2006), which was nominated
        as India's selection for the Academy Awards, and Shaheed-E-Mohabbet (1999), the film which tells the real-life story of Boota Singh.\n
        Gurdas also appeared in the hit film Shaheed Udham Singh (2000), in which he played the role of Bhagat Singh, a Sikh man
        with no prejudices based on religion, caste or creed to which many of his fans and friends testify he is in real life.
        As a singer Gurdas Maan has worked with
        music directors such as Laxmikant Pyarelal, Bappi Lahiri, Anu Malik, Nadeem Sharvan, Amar Haidipur, Charanjeet Ahuja, and Jaswant Bhanyra .\n
        He also starred alongside Juhi Chawla in the epic Des Hoyaa Pardes (2004), an emotional film illustrating the tragedies faced
        by the people of Punjab in the 1980s. He adopted the role of a son of a well-respected Jatt (farmer) Gurdev Singh Somal.
        He falls in love with a high ranking police officer’s daughter. Before the wedding, the father is murdered by separatists.
        This tale soon twists in to the inevitable demise of Gurshaan (Gurdas Maan). This movie was based on actual events.\n\n














    </string>
    <string name="akshay1">Akshay Kumar was born in Amritsar, Punjab, India on 9 September 1967. His Father Late Hari Om Bhatia
        and his mother Aruna Bhatia. He has a sister named Alka Bhatia. Akshay Kumar did schooling from Don Bosco High School, Mirik,
        Darjeeling and then
        attended on Guru Nanak Khalsa College (King’s Circle), Mumbai. Akshay Kumar House Address Prime Beach, Juhu, Mumbai.He is a producer,
        martial artist and television personality.
  In a career spanning more than twenty five years, Kumar has appeared in over a hundred Hindi films and has won several awards
  including the National Film Award for Best Actor for his performance in Rustom and two Filmfare Awards.
  Box Office India has listed Kumar as one of the most successful actors in the history of Indian cinema.
  He became the first Bollywood actor whose movies have crossed respectively the Rs 2000 crore  Rs 3000 cror in 2016  in their domestic net
  lifetime collection.Having done so, he has established himself as one of the prominent actors of the Hindi cinema.\n\n

  When he began his acting career in the 1990s, he primarily starred in action films and was known for his appearances in films of the
  Khiladi series as well as other action films such as Mohra (1994), Main Khiladi Tu Anari (1994), Sapoot (1996) and Angaaray (1998).
  Later, Kumar also gained fame for his drama, romantic and comic roles. He earned critical acclaim for his portrayal of a hysterical professor
  in Sangharsh (1999) and a criminal in Jaanwar (1999). His performances in romantic films like Dhadkan (2000), Andaaz (2003) and Namastey
  London (2007); drama films like Waqt (2005) and Bhool Bhulaiyaa (2007); comedy films like Hera Pheri (2000), Mujhse Shaadi Karogi (2004),
  Garam Masala (2005), Bhagam Bhag (2006) and Singh Is Kinng (2008) were all well received. In 2007, he starred in four consecutive
  commercially successful films. Kumar hit a rough patch since 2009 to 2011 but came back with two successes, Housefull 2 (2012) and Rowdy
  Rathore (2012) with both of them grossing over ₹1 billion (US$16 million). His other films like OMG (2012), Special 26 (2012), Holiday
  (2014) and Gabbar Is Back (2015) were highly successful critically and commercially.
  From January 2016 to August 2017, he starred in five domestic net ₹100 crore plus grossers in a row with films \n
        1. Airlift (2016)\n
        2.Housefull 3 (2016)\n
        3. Rustom (2016)\n
        4.Jolly LLB 2 (2017)\n
        5.Toilet: Ek Prem Katha (2017)\n\n
    Akshay Kumar Married to Actress Twinkle Khanna on 17 January 2001. The couple have a son named Aarav and a daughter named Nitara.
        Akshay Kumar had relationship with Actress Pooja Batra,
        Raveena Tandon, Shilpa Shetty and Twinkle Khanna. He is Hindu by Religion and His Nationality Indian and Star Sign Virgo.
\n\n</string>
    <string name="about1"> The word Punjab is made of two words Punj (Five) + Aab (Water) i.e. land of five rivers.
        It is named so because of the five rivers flowing through this land and these five rivers of Punjab are Sutlej, Beas, Ravi,
        Chenab and Jhelum. Historically, Punjab was the name of the region containing today states of Punjab (Pakistan), Punjab (India),Haryana,Himachal Pradesh
        and Delhi. The rivers flowing through this region are an important geographical feature of this land, thus made this region popular with the name
        "land of five rivers" or "punjab". As of today, only two rivers Sutlej and Beas flow through Punjab state in India. The third river Ravi flows partially in Punjab,
        mainly along the international boundry of India and Pakistan and then enters Pakistan. The other two rivers Chenab and Jhelum flow in the Punjab state in Pakistan.
        All these five rivers are tributaries of Indus river.All these five rivers finally merge into Indus river directly or indirectly and the Indus then terminates
        into Arabian Sea near Karachi city in Pakistan. These rivers, including the Indus river are considered part of Indus Valley River System.\n\n
       </string>
    <string name="punjab1">The Punjab region was home to the Indus Valley Civilization until 1900 BCE. In 1800 BCE the Aryans invaded northern
        India. The Punjab was conquered by Alexander the Great in 330 BCE and was captured by Chandragupta Maurya. The Punjab was home to the
        Gupta Empire, the enpire of the Alchon Huns, the empire of Harsha, and the Mongol Empire. Circa 1000, the Punjab was invaded by
        Muslims and was part of the Delhi Sultanate and Mughal Empire. Sikhism originated in Punjab and resulted in the formation of the Sikh
        Confederacy after the fall of the Mughal Empire. The confederacy was united into the Sikh Empire by Ranjit Singh. The entire Punjab
        region was annexed by the British East India Company from the Sikh Empire in 1849. In 1947, the Punjab Province of British India was
        divided along religious lines into West Punjab and East Punjab. The western part was assimilated into new country of Pakistan while
        the east stayed in India. The Indian Punjab was divided on the basis of language in 1966. It was divided into 3 parts. Haryanvi
        speaking areas (dialect of Hindi) were carved out as Haryana, Hilly regions and Pahari speaking areas formed Himachal Pradesh
         alongside the current state of Punjab. The diverse cultures of the various rulers of Punjab have influenced Punjabi culture.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="punjab2">The government of Punjab has three branches - executive, judiciary and legislative. Punjab follows the
        parliamentary system of government with the Chief Minister as the head of the state. \n \n</string>
    <string name="punjab4">State is primarily agriculture-based due to the presence of abundant water sources and fertile soils
        Other major industries include the manufacturing of scientific instruments, agricultural goods, electrical goods, financial
        services, machine tools, textiles, sewing machines, sports goods, starch, tourism, fertilisers, bicycles, garments, and the processing
        of pine oil and sugar. Minerals and energy resources also contribute to the Punjab economy although to a much lesser extent. Punjab
        has the largest number of steel rolling mill plants in India, which are located in "Steel Town"—Mandi Gobindgarh in the Fatehgarh
        Sahib district.
    </string>
    <string name="potics1"> The current Government was elected in the 2017 Assembly elections as Congress won
        77 out of 117 Assembly seats and Amarinder Singh is the current Chief Minister.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="polotics3"> <b>List of chief Minister of punjab. </b>
        \n
        1.Gopi Chand Bhargava \n
        2.Bhim Sen Sachar \n
        3.Partap Singh Kairon \n
        4.Ram Kishan \n
        5.Giani Gurmukh Singh Musafir \n
        6.Gurnam Singh \n
        7.Lachhman Singh Gill \n
        8.Parkash Singh Badal \n
        9.Zail Singh \n
        10.Darbara Singh \n
        11.Surjit Singh Barnala \n
        12.Beant Singh \n
        13.Harcharan Singh Brar \n
        14.Rajinder Kaur Bhattal \n
        15.Amarinder Singh \n\n</string>
    <string name="polotics5">The main players in the politics of the state are the Indian National Congress and the Shiromani Akali Dal (with alliance Bharatiya Janata Party).
        The present government is headed by Amarinder Singh. President rule has been imposed in Punjab 8 times so far, since 1950, for different reasons. In terms of the
        absolute number of days, Punjab was under President’s rule for 3510 days, which is about 10 years.Much of this was in the 80s during the height of militancy in Punjab.
        Punjab was under President’s rule for 5 continuous years from 1987 to 1992.Each district under the administrative control of a District Collector. The districts are
        subdivided into 79 tehsils, which have fiscal and administrative powers over settlements within their borders, including maintenance of local land records comes under
        the administrative control of a Tehsildar. Each Tehsil consists of blocks which are total 143 in number. The blocks consist of revenue villages. There are total number
        of revenue villages in the state is 12,278. There are 22 Zila Parishads, 136 Municipal Committees and 22 Improvement Trusts looking after
        143 towns and 14 cities of Punjab. Majitha is newly created tehsil, which was formed in September 2016. Zirakpur is the latest sub-tehsil, in the district of Mohali.\n\n

































    </string>
    <string name="food1">Punjabi cuisine is associated with food from the Punjab region of India and Pakistan.
        This cuisine has a rich tradition of many distinct and local ways of cooking.
        One is a special form of tandoori cooking that is now famous in other parts of India, UK, Canada, and in many parts
        of the world.The local cuisine of Punjab is heavily influenced by the agriculture and farming lifestyle prevalent from the times
        of the ancient Harappan Civilization. Locally grown staple foods form the major part of the local cuisine. Distinctively Punjabi
        cuisine is known for its rich, buttery flavours along with the extensive vegetarian and meat dishes.
        Main dishes include Sarson ka saag (a stew whose main ingredient is mustard greens) and makke ki roti
        (flatbreads made with cornmeal).Basmati rice is the indigenous variety of Punjab and many varieties of rice dishes have been developed
        with this variety. Many vegetable and meat based dishes are developed for this type of rice.\n\n</string>
    <string name="food2">There are many styles of cooking in Punjab. In the villages many people still employ the traditional
        infrastructure for cooking purposes. This includes wood-fired and masonry ovens. In the past many people employed wood-burning stoves.
        But this method is dying out. One derivation from this type of cooking is the tandoori style of cooking commonly known as tandoor.
        In India, tandoori cooking is traditionally associated with Punjab as Punjabis embraced the tandoor on a regional level.
        This style of cooking became popular in the mainstream after the 1947 partition when Punjabis resettled in places such as Delhi.
        In rural Punjab, it is common to have communal tandoors, which are also called Kath tadoors in Punjabi.\n\n</string>
    <string name="food5">Punjab is a major producer of wheat, rice and dairy products. These products also form the staple diet of the
        Punjabi people. The state of Punjab has one of the highest capita usage of dairy products in India.Therefore, dairy products form
        an important component of Punjabi diet.Punjab is considered to second lagrest production of wheat and fouth largest in case of Rice.</string>
    <string name="dance1">The term Bhaṅgra refers to the traditional dance from the Indian subcontinent originating in the Majha area of the Punjab region,
        free form traditional Bhangra originating in Punjab, India and modern Bhangra developed by the Punjabi diaspora.
        The origins of traditional Bhangra are speculative. According to Dhillon (1998), Bhangra is related to the Punjabi dance bagaa
        which is a martial dance of Punjab.However, the folk dance of Majha originated in Sialkot and took root in Gujranwalla,
        Sheikhupur, Gujrat (districts in Punjab, Pakistan) and Gurdaspur. The traditional form of
        Bhangra danced in the villages of Sialkot district is regarded as the standard.Although the main districts where traditional
        Bhangra is performed are in Punjab, Pakistan, the community form of traditional Bhangra has been maintained in Gurdaspur district,
        Punjab, India and has been maintained by people who have settled in Hoshiarpur, Punjab India after leaving what is now Punjab,
        Pakistan. Traditional Bhangra is performed in a circle and is performed using traditional dance steps.
        Traditional Bhangra is now also performed on occasions other than during the harvest season and is popular in Pakistan.\n\n




    </string>
    <string name="dance9">Traditional Bhangra has also been imported into the Jammu plains which merge with the plains of Punjab,together
        with other Punjabi folk dances such as Giddha and Luddi.Punjabi language influences
        can be observed when people dance such dances in Jammu as the area falls within the Punjab region and shares an affinity with Punjab.
        The 1950s saw the development of the free form traditional Bhangra in Punjab, India which was patronised by the Maharaja of Patiala
        who requested a staged performance of Bhangra in 1953. The first significant developers of this style were a dance troupe led by
        brothers from the Deepak family of Sunam (Manohar, Avtar and Gurbachan) and the dhol player Bhana Ram Sunami.[19] Free form
        traditional Bhangra developed during stage performances which incorporate traditional Bhangra moves and also include sequences
        from other Punjabi dances, namely, Luddi, Jhummar, Dhamaal, and Gham Luddi. The singing of Punjabi folk songs, bolian, are
        incorporated from Malwai Giddha.
        Bhangra competitions have been held in Punjab, India for many decades, with Mohindra College in Patiala being involved in the 1950s.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="dance2">
        1.Sammi \n
        2.Giddha \n
        3.Jaago\n
        4.Kikli \n \n
    </string>
    <string name="dance7">1.Bhangra \n
                          2.Malwai Giddha \n
                        3.Jhumar \n
                        4.Mirza \n
                        5.Sial Koti \n
                        6.Jugni \n
                        7.Khichan \n
                        8.Dhamal \n
                        9.Dankara \n
                        10.Khatka (Sword Dance) \n \n</string>
    <string name="dance5">1.Bhangra \n
                           2. Karthi \n
                            3.Jindua \n
                            4.Dandass \n \n \n \n </string>
    <string name="clothing1">In the ancient Punjab region, people wore cotton clothing. The tops for both sexes reached to the knees.
        A scarf was worn over the tops which would be draped over the left shoulder and under the right. A large sheet would be further
        draped over one shoulder which would hang loose towards the knees. Both sexes wore a dhoti around the waist.
        Modern Punjabi dress has retained this outfit but over its long history has added other forms of dress.
        The Punjab region had a flourishing industry in cotton during the 19th and early 20th centuries, when various
        kinds of coarse cotton cloths including lungi, khes, datahi, chadders, coasting, shirting, curtains, susi, tehmats, durris,
        towels, dusters, patkas etc. were manufactured in Hoshiarpur, Gurdaspur, Peshawar, Lahore, Multan, Amritsar, Ludhiana, Jhang,
        Shahpur, Jalandhar, Delhi, Gurgaon, Rohtak, Karnal, Rewari, Panipat etc.This cotton industry added to the richness of Punjabi
        clothing which exhibits Punjab rich and vibrant culture in its dresses.
        Various types of dresses are worn based on different Punjabi festivals, local events and ceremonies.\n\n




    </string>
    <string name="cloth9">
                        1	Kurta \n
                           \t\t\t 1.1	Multani kurta\n
                           \t\t\t 1.2	Punjabi phulkari kurta \n
                            \t\t\t 1.3	Punjabi bandhani kurta \n
                            \t\t\t  1.4	Muktsari kurta \n
                        2	Salwar suit \n
                        3	Punjabi Tamba and Kurta \n
                        4	Kurti \n
                        5	Pothohari suit \n
                        6	Chola \n
                        7	Choga \n
                        8	Punjabi salwar suit \n
                        9	Punjabi ghagra \n
                        10	Punjabi Juti \n
                        11	Patiala salwar \n
                        12	Saraiki shalwar suits \n
                          \t\t\t 12.1 Bahawalpuri shalwar suit \n
                          \t\t\t 12.2 Multani shalwar suit \n
                        13	Phulkari \n \n</string>
    <string name="festival">Punjabi festivals are various festive celebrations observed by Punjabis in Pakistan, India and
        the diaspora Punjabi community found worldwide. The Punjabis are a diverse group of people from different religious
        background that affects the festivals they observe. According to a 2007 estimate, the total population of Punjabi Muslims
        is about 90 million  with 97% of Punjabis who live in Pakistan following Islam,
        in contrast to the remaining 30 million Punjabi Sikhs and Punjabi Hindus who predominantly live in India.
    The Punjabi Muslims typically observe the Islamic festivals, do not observe Hindu or Sikh religious festivals, and in
        Pakistan the official holidays recognize only the Islamic festivals. The Punjabi Sikhs and Hindus typically do not observe
        these, and instead observe historic festivals such as Lohri, Basant and Baisakhi as seasonal festivals.The Sikh and Hindu
        festivals are regional official holidays in India,
        as are major Islamic festivals.Other seasonal Punjabi festivals in India include Teejon (Teeyan) and Maghi.\n\n</string>
    <string name="fest2">The Punjabi Muslim festivals are set according to the lunar Islamic calendar (Hijri),
        and the date falls earlier by 10 to 13 days from year to year.The Hindu and Sikh Punjabi seasonal festivals
        are set on specific dates of the luni-solar Bikrami calendar or Punjabi calendar
        and the date of the festival also typically varies in the Gregorian calendar but stays within the same two Gregorian months.\n\n</string>
    <string name="fest8">1.Holi \n
                        2.Lohri \n
                        3.Maghi \n
                        4.Basant Panchami \n
                        5.Vaisakhi\n
                        6.Diwali\n
                        7.Gurpurav\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="golden_temple1">Sri Harmandir Sahib also known as Golden Temple and the Darbar Sahib, is the holiest Gurdwara and
        the most important pilgrimage site of Sikhism.It is located in the city of Amritsar, Punjab, India.
        The temple is built around a man-made pool (sarovar) that was completed by Guru Ram Das in 1577.
        The temple is spiritually the most significant shrine in Sikhism. It became a center of the Singh
        Sabha Movement between 1883 and 1920s.
    </string>
    <string name="jaliawala3">Jallianwala Bagh is a public garden in Amritsar in the Punjab state of India,
        and houses a memorial of national importance, established in 1951 by the Government of India, to commemorate the massacre
        of peaceful celebrators including unarmed women and children by British occupying forces,
        on the occasion of the Punjabi New Year on April 13, 1919 in the Jallianwala Bagh. </string>
    <string name="dugyana1">he Durgiana Temple, also known as Lakshmi Narayan Temple, Durga Tirath and Sitla Mandir, is a premier temple situated in the city of
        Amritsar, Punjab, India. Though a Hindu temple, its architecture is similar to the Golden Temple of Sikh religion.This temple derives its name from
        the Goddess Durga,
        the chief Goddess deified and worshipped here. Idols of Goddess Laksmi (goddess of wealth) and Vishnu (the protector of the world) are also deified here
        and worshipped.The temple is situated near the Lohgarh gate, in Amritsar, in the Indian state of Punjab . It is very close to the Amritsar Railway station, and is about 1.5 kilometres (0.93 mi)
        from the bus station. Amritsar is well connected by road, rail and air services with the rest of the country
    </string>
    <string name="attari1">The border is located 24 kilometres (15 mi) from Lahore and 32 kilometres (20 mi)
        from Amritsar. It is also 3 kilometres (1.9 mi) from the bordering village of Attari.
    The reason why the border is called Wagah is because there is a village also named Wagah in Pakistan, is near which the accepted
        Radcliffe Line, the boundary demarcation line dividing India and Pakistan upon the Partition of India, was drawn
    The village lies 600 meters west of the border. At the time of independence in 1947,
        the migrants from the Indian parts of the subcontinent entered the present day Pakistan through this border crossing


    </string>
    <string name="mansa1">Mata Mansa Devi is a Hindu temple dedicated to goddess Mansa Devi, a form of Shakti, chandigarh in India.
        The temple complex is spread of 100 acres (0.40 km2) of the Shivalik foothills in village Bilaspur, near Mani Majra, and Panchkula, 10 km from Chandi Mandir.
    It is one of the prominent Shakti temples of North India. Thousands of devotees visit the shrine from various parts of the country, and especially during the
        Navratra mela, this number rises to lakhs everyday for the nine auspicious days.</string>
    <string name="devitla1">Devi Talab Mandir is dedicated to Godess Durga and is believed to be at least 200 years old.
        Mata Tripurmalini Mandir is situated within the temple premises and is among the 51 Shakti Peethas of India.
    Devi Talab Mandir is dedicated to Goddess Durga and is believed to be at least 200 years old. Mata
        Tripurmalini Mandir is situated within the temple premises and is among the 51 Shakti Peethas of India.</string>
    <string name="religion1">Sikhism forms the main religion of Punjab in India. Founded by Guru Nanak Dev and other nine Gurus,
        it forms the fifth largest religion in the world. The main faith of Sikhism is in "Waheguru” meaning the Universal God.The religion preaches attainment of salvationthrough disciplined and personal meditation of the Almighty. Sikhs worshipthe ten Gurus and Guru Granth Sahib, the Holy Scripture that is revered as the eleventh and final Guru. Sikhism stresses on monotheism and non-anthropomorphic concept of God. Charity work and community services are considered to be crucial ina person's life. Hard work and true dedication is regarded as the basic guideline to lead one's life. Punjab abounds in gurdwaras, which form the principal center of worship for the Sikhs.The Golden Temple of Amritsar is a world famous pilgrimage center, which attracts flocks of devotees from across the globe.
    </string>
    <string name="hindu1">Hinduism, though not as widely prevalent as the Sikhism, is a prominent religion of Punjab.
        In fact, it is the second most prominent religion practiced in the state. The Hindus have a liberal lifestyle and most
        of them even worship in gurdwaras. They are mostly into trade and commerce. The most common castes in Hinduism, as prevalent
        in Punjab, are Khatri (Kshatriya in Hindi), Brahman, Baniya and Rajput.
        The important Hindu sects are the Sanatan Dharmis, Arya Samajis, Radhaswamis, Nanak Panthis and Ecumenical Hinduism.\n</string>
    <string name="others1">Islam forms another important religion in Punjab, though there is only a minority following the same.
        After the partition in 1947, most of the Muslims in Punjab migrated to Pakistan. Despite the few followers of Islam, one can
        easily find good number of mosques in the state. Christianity, Jainism and Buddhism form other minority religions of the state.</string>
    <string name="religion5">According to the 2011 Census of India, Punjab, India has a population of around 27.7 million. Sikhism is the
        most practiced faith in Punjab, and 57.69% of the population belongs to the Sikh faith.
        Around 38.49% of the population practices Hinduism. Other faiths include Islam, Buddhism, Christianity and Jainism \t

        At least one Sikh Gurdwara can be found in every village, town and city


    </string>
    <string name="music1"> Punjabi music has a diverse style of music, ranging from folk and Sufi to classical.
    Folk music of the Punjab is the traditional music of Punjab produced using the traditional musical instruments like Tumbi, Algoze, Dhadd, Sarangi, Chimta and more.
        There is a wide range of folk songs for every occasion from birth to death including marriage, festivals, fairs and religious ceremonies.
    unjabi songs in recent years has entered mainstream Indian culture, as well as in the UK and U.S. Its inclusion in Bollywood songs. The rise in popularity in Punjabi music in London and in the suburb of Southall, which has a sizeable South Asian population, can be attributed to the diaspora of immigrants from both to east and west Punjab to the United Kingdom in the 1970s.
        By the 1980s, Punjabi music, many types of which were now being referred to as “bhangra,” started to be played in discos.\n
unjabi songs in recent years has entered mainstream Indian culture, as well as in the UK and U.S. Its inclusion in Bollywood songs. The rise in popularity in Punjabi music in London and in the suburb of Southall, which has a sizeable South Asian population, can be attributed to the diaspora of immigrants from both to east and west Punjab to the United Kingdom in the 1970s.
        By the 1980s, Punjabi music, many types of which were now being referred to as “bhangra,” started to be played in discos

    </string>
    <string name="education1">The Indian government lays emphasis on the primary education up to the age of fourteen years, referred
        to as elementary education in India.The Indian government has also banned child labour in order to ensure that the children
        do not enter unsafe working conditions.However, both free education and the ban on child labour are difficult to enforce due
        to economic disparity and social conditions.80% of all recognized schools at the elementary stage are government run or
        supported, making it the largest provider of education in the country. \n \n</string>
    <string name="educatioon4">However, due to a shortage of resources and lack of political will, this system suffers from massive
        gaps including high pupil to teacher ratios, shortage of infrastructure and poor levels of teacher training. Figures released
        by the Indian government in 2011 show that there were 5,816,673 elementary school teachers in India.As of March 2012 there
        were 2,127,000 secondary school teachers in India.Education has also been made free
        for children for 6 to 14 years of age or up to class VIII under the Right of Children to Free and Compulsory Education Act 2009</string>
    <string name="uni1">Punjab is served by many public institutes of higher education or Universities.
    All the major arts, humanities, science, engineering, law, medicine, veterinary science, and business courses are offered,
            leading to first degrees as well as postgraduate awards. Advanced research is conducted in all major areas of excellence.
        Punjab Agricultural University is one of the world's leading authorities in agriculture.\n

    </string>
    <string name="state">1.Panjab University, Chandigarh (Punjab State University)\n
                          2.Baba Farid University of Health Sciences(Faridkot)\n
                           3.Guru Nanak Dev University(Amritsar)\n
                           4. Punjab Agricultural University(Ludhiana)\n
                           5. IK Gujral Punjab Technical University(Jalandhar)\n
                           6. Maharaja Ranjit Singh State Technical University(Bathinda)\n
                           7. Punjabi University(Patiala)\n
                           8. Guru Ravidas Ayurved University(Hoshiarpur)\n
                           9. Guru Angad Dev Veterinary and Animal Sciences University(Ludhiana)\n
                           10.Rajiv Gandhi National University of Law(Patiala)\n
</string>
    <string name="univer1">1.Apeejay Institute of Management Technical Campus, Jalandhar\n
                            2.Sri Guru Granth Sahib World University, Fatehgarh Sahib\n
                            3.GGS College of Modern Technology, Kharar\n
                            4.Indian School of Business, Ajitgarh\n
                            5.Guru Kashi University, Talwandi Sabo\n
                            6.DAV University, Jalandhar\n
                            7.GNA University, Phagwara\n
                            8.Sant Baba Bhag Singh University, Jalandhar\n
                            9.Akal University\n
                            10.<b>Lovely Professional University</b>\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="collages1">There are many schools in Punjab with a bright and famous history and many of them are well known for their
        facilities and education. Some are affiliated to CBSE(Central Board of Secondry Education) or ICSE(The Indian Certificate of Secondary Education )
        or regional Board. But some of you may be having problems in choosing the right school to get admission into.
        So to avoid the confusion and select the most appropriate one out of all the schools we have made this list of top schools in Punjab.


    </string>
    <string name="fauna1">Few of the local rivers in Punjab also have the dangerous species of Crocodiles. The extraction of
        silk from silkworms is also another industry that flourishes in the state. Production of bee honey is also done in some parts
        of Punjab. The southern plains in Punjab is desert land hence camel can also be seen. Buffaloes can be seen grazing around the
        banks of river. The north eastern part has animals like horses. The desert area also has dangerous species of snakes like cobra
        and sangehur. The wild life sanctuaries have species of wild animals like otter, wild
         boar, wildcat, fruit bat, hog deer, flying fox, squirrel and mongoose.\n\n

        Baaz also known as the Eastern Goshawk and Blackbuck known as Antilope cervicapra are the state bird and state animal
        of Punjab respectively. The Shisham known as Dalbergia Sissoo is the state tree of state of Punjab.\n\n

        The natural formed forests can be seen in the Shivalik ranges of Punjab area in the districts like Ropar, Gurdaspur a
        nd Hoshiarpur. Patiala has the Bir forest while wetlands area in state of Punjab has the famous Mand forest.\n\n

        There are a number of botanical gardens spread in various areas of Punjab. There is also a zoological park
        and a tiger safari park. There are a total of 3 parks dedicated to deer.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="haran1">
Harmanpreet Kaur  is an Indian woman cricket player.She was born on 8 March 1989 Moga, Punjab, India.She made her ODI debut
        at age of 20 against Pakistan., she made her Twenty20 International debut in 2009 ICC Women’s World Twenty20
        opposite to England.She made her debut as captain against Pakistan  as India defended 81 runs thus won Asia Cup.\n\n
        <b>Earlier Life: \n</b>
            Kaur was born on 8 March 1989 in Moga, Punjab, to Harmandar Singh Bhullar, a volleyball and basketball player and Satwinder Kaur.
        Her parents are baptised Sikhs. Her younger sister Hemjeet, is post-graduate in English and works as an assistant professor at
        Guru Nanak College in Moga.She took to cricket after joining the Gian Jyoti School Academy, 30 kilometres (19 mi) away from her
        residence in Moga, where she trained under Kamaldeesh Singh Sodhi. Harman used to play with men in the formative days of her career.
        She moved to Mumbai in 2014 where she began working for the Indian Railways.Harmanpreet was inspired by Virender Sehwag.\n\n
    <b>Facts about Harmanpreet Kaur:\n</b>
        1.Teams Played for: Leicestershire Women, Punjab Women, Railways Women, Sydney Thunders Women, Indian Women Team.\n
        2.Harmanpreet made her debut against Pakistan in 2009 at the age of just 20.\n
        3.In June 2009, She made her T20I debut against England’s Women Team in T20I World Cup Tournament.\n
        4.She was named as Indian women’s captain for the 2012 Women’s Twenty20 Asia Cup final, as captain Mithali Raj
        and vice-captain Jhulan Goswami were out because of injuries.\n
        5. In August 2014, she one of the eight debut that played against England women cricket team in
        a Test match at Sir Paul Getty’s Ground, Wormsle.
        6. In November 2015, Harmanpreet Kaur took 9 wickets in a test match against South Africa Women Team\n
        7.In June 2016, she became the first Indian cricketer to be signed by an overseas Twenty20 franchise.
        Sydney Thunder, the Women’s Big Bash League champions, signed her for the 2016–17 season \n\n
        <b>Awards:\n</b>
        1.Arjuna Award for Cricket



    </string>
    <string name="satnam1">Satnam Singh Bhamara (born December 10, 1995) is an Indian professional basketball player.
        He became the first player from India to be drafted into the NBA when the Dallas Mavericks chose him with the 52nd
        overall pick in the 2015 NBA draft. With 7 ft 2 in (2.18 m) and 290 lb (132 kg), Singh plays the center position.
        He played high school basketball at IMG Academy, a private athletic training institute headquartered in Bradenton, Florida.
        He attracted attention from media outlets since he was as young as 14 years old, and his career at IMG helped put him on
        the radar for NBA teams.\n\n

    <b>Earlier Life:\n</b>
        Satnam singh was born on December 10, 1995, in Baloke, a village located in the Barnala district of Punjab, India that had a population of
        only about 800.Both Singh father, Balbir, and his paternal grandfather were wheat farmers and millers, and the family
        house was located four miles from the closest paved road. In the mid-1980s, while in his childhood, Singh father became the
        tallest person in his village and his tremendous height caused the general public to advise him to start playing basketball in
        cities that had the proper facilities. The sport received little interest in India compared to cricket, the sport of field hockey,
        and soccer, however, and his father denied these overtures and wanted his son to follow his footsteps as a farmer.
        Balbir stayed in his hometown and was elected head of the village. He married and had three children, the middle child being Satnam\n\n
        At 9 years old, Singh was taller than the majority of adults in his village. His father took him to a local basketball court at
        around this time, despite having a meager understanding of the game. Singh was under the impression that he was being taken to play
        volleyball, and he struggled to play. Nevertheless, Singh continued to play using a hoop his father mounted in a dirt courtyard near
        his house. After drawing interest from villagers, who would occasionally come to watch him, he earned the nickname "Chhotu" among the
        villagers in his hometown, which meant "little one" in his native tongue, as his rapid growth made the basketball seem to shrink in his
        hands over time. Singh interest in the game prompted his father to search for players and coaches in the Punjab region. Singh participated
        in youth leagues in Punjab and quickly began to dominate his opponents. At age 10, his father was urged to enroll him in the Ludhiana Basketball
        Academy (LBA) in
        the large Punjabi city of Ludhiana,a school designed to develop talent in 14- to 18-year-olds from Punjab and its neighboring states.\n\n
        Talwinderjit Singh was one of the many future members of the junior and senior Indian national basketball teams that the academy had experience
        working with.At the LBA, Singh was taught some of his first basketball skills and drills by former Punjab basketball coach and Sports Authority of India
        director Dr. Sankaran Subramanian.When he was 13 years old, Singh was 6 ft 11 in (2.11 m) tall, 230 lb (104 kg), and wore size-18 shoes.
        As he began getting more exposure to professional basketball and the National Basketball Association (NBA), he began to idolize stars such as Kobe Bryant and
        would try to model his game after Yao Ming and Dwight Howard.Outside of the league, he looked up to Ludhiana alum, Jagdeep Singh Bains


    </string>
    <string name="milkha1">Milkha Singh is a former Indian track and field sprinter who was the first Indian male athlete to win an
        individual athletics gold medal at a Commonwealth Games. Fondly called ‘The Flying Sikh’—a title bequeathed to him by the
        former President of Pakistan, General Ayub Khan—he is highly respected for his sporting achievements. He has made his motherland
        proud by winning several Gold medals in international sporting events like the Commonwealth Games and Asian Games.
        He had entered the 400m race at the 1960 Olympic Games as one of the favorites and had even led the race till the 200m mark
        before he lost his speed and other runners overtook him. Sadly, the contender for Gold couldn’t even win a Bronze! Yet even
        in losing he set an Indian national record for 400m. Milkha Singh’s story is one of hope and inspiration. As a teenager he
        witnessed the massacre of his whole family in front of his eyes. Orphaned and heart-broken he worked up his way through life,
        seeking solace in the running.After years of struggle he became a successful man and today he
        supports needy sportsmen through the Milkha Singh Charitable trust.\n\n
        <b>Early Life:\n</b>
            He was born into a Sikh Rathore Rajput family in Punjab, in undivided India during the pre-independence days.
            He was one of 15 siblings, many of whom died during childhood.The partition of Indian happened when he was still a teenager.
        In the violence that ensued, he witnessed
        the killings of his parents and several siblings before his very eyes. His father, as he lay dying told Milkha to run for his life.
        Hindus and Sikhs were targeted and mercilessly killed in Punjab. He escaped to Delhi in 1947. Thankfully he had
        a married sister living there who helped him in his rehabilitation.
He was very heart broken and disillusioned after losing so many members of his family and he considered becoming a
        dacoit. However, one of his brothers advised him to join the army instead.\n\n
        <b>Awards and Achievements:\n</b>
        1.In the year 1958 alone, he won many major events. He won the Gold medals
        in the 200m and 400m competitions at the Asian Games and Gold at the 440 yards event in Commonwealth Games.\n
        2.He was given the Padma Shri, India’s fourth highest civilian award, in 1959 for his glorious achievements in the field of sports.
        3.He won Gold medals in 400m and 4x400m relay in 1962 Asian Games.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="prem1">Prem Chopra is an actor in Hindi and Punjabi films. Prem Chopra was born to a Hindu Punjabi family in Lahore
        on 23 September 1935 to Ranbirlal and Rooprani Chopra. He was third of six children.His father worked at the attorney-generals
        office. He was brought up in Shimla. His father wanted him to be a IAS officer but Chopra pursued performing arts in College
        and graduated in arts from Punjab University. Shimla had a strong theater movement in the period 1957-1961 and Chopra reveled
        in it. He watched a lot of Hindi and English movies and, after graduation, came to Bombay in the early 1960 and joined the Times
        of India circulation department due to his art degree. Simultaneously, he kept visiting studios and tried to get a break in films.\n\n
        He kept trying to get a break in films. Prem Chopra made his debut in Bollywood with the Bharat Bhushan-starer Mud Mud Ke Na Dekh in
        1960, which didnt do well. In 1960 he got a Punjabi film Chaudhary Karnail Singh , the film won a National Award and got
        Prem noticed.But he didnt have much hit Hindi films till 1964 with exception of his debut Punjabi film Karnail Singh and Sapni.\n\n
        Next in 1964 he played Sukhdev in Shaheed, one of his rare positive leading roles which became hit.His performances from 1965-67
        in hit films like Sikandar E Azam ,Nishan,Kunwari,Teesri Manzil ,Mera Saaya and Upkar showcased his versatility. After Teesri Manzil
        and Upkaar he was flooded with films as a villain. Prem Chopra continued working with TOI, when already he was part of box-office
        hits like Nishan,Sikandar E Azam in 1965 and Sagaai, Mera Saaya in 1966. After Upkaar in 1967 he left The Times of India. As a villain,
        he gained fame all round India when he acted with Superstar Rajesh Khanna in Do Raaste. The duo of Rajesh-Prem worked in 19
        films from 1969 till Ghar Parivaar in 1991.In the critically acclaimed comedy film Hulchul (1971), played the lead hero in this
        suspense thriller and was not a villain and Prem was leading man in Kunwari(1966), Samaj Ko Badal Dalo(1970).
        Prem Chopra played the main lead in 1970 box-office hit small budget comedy film Samaj Ko Badal Dalo as lead hero and was paired
        opposite Tamil actresses Kanchana and Shardha.\n\n
        <b>Movies by Prem chopra:\n</b>
        1. Shaheed (1965)\n
        2. Sikander-e-Azam (1965)\n
        3. Kunwari (1966)\n
        4.Upkaar (1967)\n
        5.Do Raaste (1969)\n
        6.Purab Aur Pachhim(1970)\n
        7.Kati Patang (1970)\n
        8.Keemat(1973)\n
        9.Ajanabee(1974)\n
        10.Prem Nagar(1974)\n
        11.Kaala Sona (1975)\n
        12. Mehbooba(1976)\n
        13. Do Anjaane (1976)\n
        14. Jaadu Tona (1977)\n
        15.Tyaag (1977)\n
        16.Dostana(1980)\n
        17.Kranti (1981)\n
        18.Souten, Oonche Log (1985)\n
        19.Phool Bane Angaarey (1991)\n
        20.Bewaffa Se Waffa(1992)\n
    </string>
    <string name="man1">Manmohan singh is an Indian economist and politician who served as the Prime Minister of India from 2004 to 2014. The
  first Sikh in office, Singh was also the first prime minister since Jawaharlal Nehru to be re-elected after completing a full five-year term.
 Born in Gah (now in Punjab, Pakistan), Singh\'\s family migrated to India during its partition in 1947. After obtaining his
  doctorate in economics from Oxford, Singh worked for the United Nations during 1966–69. He subsequently began his bureaucratic career
  when Lalit Narayan Mishra hired him as an advisor in the Ministry of Commerce and Industry. Over the 70s and 80s, Singh held several key
  posts in the Government of India,such as Chief Economic Advisor (1972–76), Reserve Bank governor (1982–85) and Planning Commission head
  (1985–87).\n\n Dr Manmohan Singh Scholarships are awards available to Indian students for doctoral study at St John College at the University of
        Cambridge and for undergraduate studies at the university.The Scholarships are named in honor of Manmohan Singh, a former
        Prime Minister of India. Singh graduated from St John College with a First in Economics in 1957,
        went on to earn a PhD from the University of Oxford in 1962, and was awarded an Honorary Doctorate
        by the University of Cambridge in 2006.\n\n
        <b>EDUCATION /Qualification:\n</b>
                    1.Stood first in BA (Hons), Economics, Punjab University, Chandigarh\n
                    2.1952 Stood first in MA (Economics), Punjab University, Chandigarh\n
                    3. 1954 Wright Prize for distinguished performance at St John College, Cambridge\n
                    4.1955 and 1957; Wrenbury scholar, University of Cambridge\n
                    5.1957 DPhil (Oxford), DLitt (Honoris Causa); PhD thesis on India export competitiveness\n\n
        <b>OCCUPATION /Teaching Experience:\n</b>

                1.Professor (Senior lecturer, Economics, 1957-59\n
                2. Reader, Economics, 1959-63\n
                3.Professor, Economics, Panjab University, Chandigarh, 1963-65\n
                4.Professor,International Trade, Delhi School of Economics,University of Delhi,1969-71\n
                5.Honorary professor, Jawaharlal Nehru University,New Delhi, 1976\n
                6.Delhi School of Economics, University of Delhi,1996\n\n

                <b>Working Experience/ POSITIONS:\n</b>
                        1.1971-72: Economic advisor, ministry of foreign trade\n
                        2.1972-76: Chief economic advisor, ministry of finance\n
                        3.1976-80: Director, Reserve Bank of India\n
                        4.1980-83: Chairman, India Committee of the Indo-Japan joint study committee\,
                        5. 1982-85: Alternate Governor for India, Board of governors,International Monetary Fund\n
                        6.1983-84: Member, economic advisory council to the Prime Minister\n
                        7.1985: President, Indian Economic Association\n\n
                        8.1987: Deputy Chairman, Planning Commission\n
                        9.1990: Secretary-general and commissioner, south commission, Geneva\n
                        10.1991: Advisor to the Prime Minister on economic affairs\n
                        11.1991: Chairman, UGC\n
                        12.1996: Union finance minister\n
                        13.1991: Elected to Rajya Sabha from Assam on Congress ticket\n
                        14.1995: Re-elected to Rajya Sabha\n
                        15.1996 onwards: Member, Consultative Committee for the ministry of finance\n
                        16.1996 - December 4, 1997: Chairman, Parliamentary standing committee on commerce\n
                        17.1998 onwards: Leader of the Opposition, Rajya Sabha\n
                        18. 1998 onwards: Member, committee on finance\n
                        19.1998 onwards: Member, committee on rules\n
                        20.1998-2001: Member, committee of privileges 2000 onwards: Member, executive committee, Indian parliamentary group\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="dhar1">Dharmendra is one of the biggest stars of Indian cinema. Dharmendra Deol played the romantic hero in
        woman centric films from 1960-1968 and became romantic hero from 1968-69 and played the role of action hero from 1975-1997.
        Dharmendra has appeared in 288 films. Dharmendra was among the highest paid Hindi film stars of 1970s.\n\n
        He is known as "Garam" Dharam in Bollywood. Had the looks of a real gentle man, masculine
        body of a he-man and when it came to his films, he had a very humorous touch in his dialog-delivery and the timing.\n\n
        Dharmendra's original name is Dharam Singh Deol. He was born in a Jat Sikh family in Phagwara in Kapurthala district in the
        Indian state of Punjab to Kewal Kishan Singh Deol and Satwant Kaur. He spent his early life in village Sahnewal and studied at Government
        Senior Secondary School at Lalton Kalan, Ludhiana. He did his intermediate from Ramgarhia College, Phagwara in 1952.\n\n
        <b>Awards\n</b>
        1.1991 – National Film Award for Best Popular Film Providing Wholesome Entertainment for Ghayal (producer)\n
        2.1991 – Filmfare Award for Best Movie for Ghayal.\n
        3.1997 – Filmfare Lifetime Achievement Award for his contribution to Indian Cinema.\n
        4.2012 – Padma Bhushan\n\n



</string>
    <string name="juhi1">Juhi was born in the Chawla family on November 13, 1967 in Ludhiana, Punjab, India, and is the daughter
        of Punjabi-speaking dad, Dr. S. Chawla and Gujarati-speaking mom, Mona.
        She has a brother named Sanjeev. Her mother passed away in an accident during the year 1998 while Juhi was filming "Duplicate".\n\n
        After completing her school in Ludhiana, the Chawla family moved to Bombay, Maharashtra, India, where Juhi attended
        at Sydenham College. After graduating, she entered in the Miss India competition and was crowned "Miss India 1984", taking
        over from Miss India 1983, Rekha Hande.\n\n
        Her first appearance on the tinsel screen was as Zarina in the 1986 release "Sultanat".
        She shot to fame after the release of "Qayamat Se Qayamat Tak" opposite Aamir Khan. As of August 2007,
        she has been bestowed with three awards for her performance in "Hum Hain Rahi Pyar Ke", "Duplicate", and "3 Deewarein".\n\n
        Juhi got married to multi-millionaire industrialist, Jai Mehta during the year 1998. Since then the couple have a daughter,
        Jhanvi, and son, Arjun.
        Juhi continues to act in movies, and also makes appearances in many off-beat movies, rather than the mainstream cinema with which she
        started her career.She also appears in a number of TV ad commercials.\n\n

        <b>Personal Life:\n</b>
        Juhi Chawla is married to industrialist Jay Mehta. The couple have two children: a daughter Jhanvi born in 2001 and a son Arjun born in 2003.
        In an interview Juhi revealed that Jhanvi wants to be a writer, instead of joining films.
        Jay Mehta and Juhi Chawla are the co-owners of the Indian Premier League team Kolkata Knight Riders in partnership with Shahrukh
        Khan under their company Red Chillies Entertainment. Her brother Bobby Chawla was the CEO of Red Chillies Entertainment. He suffered
        a massive stroke in 2010 after a dinner party. After being in coma for about four years, he died at Jaslok Hospital on March 9, 2014.\n\n


    </string>
    <string name="kapil1">Kapil Sharma who also titled as The Funny Man is a stand-up comedian, singer, actor and a skilful
        anchor from Amritsar Punjab India, who got popularity for his comedy show on Indian television on Colors TV “Comedy Nights
        With Kapil” but on 24, January 2016 show shut down by the Channel due to some unknown internal conflict between the Kapil and
        the channel. But He again started his journey of comedy on new channel “Sony TV”
        and this time he named his show “The Kapil Sharma Show” and today this show is much successful than his previous show.\n\n

        It was not easy for Kapil Sharma to again start his show with some new concepts and ideas because colors channel claimed that he and
        his Team can not use any of character and situation of his previous show on his new show. Otherside he had also the pressure
        of his millions of fans from worldwide who were waiting that when his show again become the routine of their weekends.\n\n
        <b>Early and personal life:\n</b>
        Kapil was born in Amritsar, Punjab. His father Jeetendra Kumar Punj was a head constable in the Punjab Police
        while his mother Janak Rani is a housewife..His father was diagnosed with cancer in 1997 and died in 2004 at AIIMS in Delhi.
        He studied at the Khalsa college in Amritsar, Punjab. Kapil Sharma has a brother named Ashok Kumar Sharma,
        who is a Police constable and a sister named Pooja Pawan Devgan. He studied in dav public school, Lawerence road, Amritsar.\n\n
        <b>Awards:\n</b>
        1.Most Entertaining TV Series - Non Fiction\n
        (Comedy Nights with Kapil (2013))\n
        2.CNN-IBN Indian of the Year(Entertainer of the Year(2013)).\n
        3.Star Guild Awards	Best Comedy Show(2014).\n
        4.Indian Television Academy Awards	Best Actor (Comedy)-2015\n













    </string>
    <string name="dev1">Dev Anand, born Dharam Dev Pishori Anand, was an iconic Hindi film actor, producer and director who began
        his acting career in 1946, with a film called Hum Ek Hain.
        Born in September 1923 in Gurdaspur, Punjab (British India), Dev Anand was the son of a well to do advocate.\n\n
        Anand graduated from the Government College, Lahore, from where he obtained a degree in English Literature.
        After completing his education in the early 1940s, Dev Anand left his hometown for Bombay where he secured a job in the military censor
        office. He also joined his older brother, Chetan Anand as a member of the Indian People Theatre Association (IPTA).
        He was soon offered a role in Hum Ek Hain in 1946 and was soon seen to be paired along with popular and established actress and
        singer Suriya. The pair starred in seven films together, like Vidya, Jeet, Do Sitare and Sangam, including others. Soon Dev Anand
        and Suriya fell in love but
        could not marry due to religious differences (Anand was Hindu and Suriya was Muslim). They stopped acting alongside after that.\n\n
        Dev Anand was offered his first big film by Ashok Kumar, who introduced him in a Bombay Talkie film, Baazi (1948)
        co-starring Kamini Kaushal, which went on to become an instant success. After the success of Baazi,
        Anand decided to become a producer and in 1949 he launched his own banner called Navketan, and which by 2011, had produced 35 films.\n\n
        In 1955, Dev Anand chose legendary Bollywood actor and director Guru Dutt to direct his film Baazi, which he was producing and acting in.
        The film saw the debut of Kalpana Karthik and starred Dev Anand and Geeta Bali. Following the huge success of this trendsetting film,
        Dev Anand and Kalpana Kathik were offered many films together and eventually the onscreen couple fell in love during the filming of Taxi
        Driver and Dev Anand proposed marriage to Kalpana Kathik.
        The couple got married in a quiet ceremony in 1954 and in 1956 had a son named Suniel.\n\n
        <b>Awards and Achievements:\n</b>
            1. In 1959 Won Filmfare Award for Best Actor (Kala Pani).\n
            2. IN 1961 Filmfare Award for Best Actor(Kala Bazar).\n
            3.IN 1962 Filmfare Award for Best Actor(Hum Dono).\n
            4.IN 1965 Filmfare Award for Best Actor(Guide).\n
            5.IN 1993	Won Lifetime Achievement Award\n
            6.IN 1993	Won Lifetime Achievement Award\n
            7.IN 1997 	Won Lifetime Achievement Award\n
            8.IN  2001Won Special Award For his contribution to Indian cinema.






    </string>
    <string name="dara1">Dara Singh was born 19 November 1928 Aged 83 Years in Amristar, Punjab Province, British, India.
        He died 12 July 2012 in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India. His Cause of Death Heart Attack. Dara Singh other names Rustam-e-Hind or
        Ironman of Indian Cinema or
        The Original Muscle Man of Bollywood. He was very popular Film Actor, Professional Wrestler and Politician.\n\n
    Dara Singh was began his film acting career in 1952 with Film Sangdil. He has acted in more than 100 Films and also appeared
        some films as Director and producer. Beside acting career, He also a very popular Wrestler of India. Dara Singh win many
        Wrestling match and worked for movies. Dara Singh married to Bachno Kaur (m. 1937-50) and Surjit Kaur in 1961 to his death.\n\n
        ara Singh first film name is Sangdil released in 1952. Some of the famous films in which Dara Singh acted are Aandhi Aur Toofan (1963),
        Rustom-E-Hind (1965), Sher Dil (1965), Lootera (1965), Dada (1966), Toofan (1969), Mera Naam Joker (1970), Anand (1971), Lalkaar (1972),
        Mard (1985), Karma (1986), Ramayan (1986 - TV SERIAL),
        Mahabharat (1988- TV SERIAL), Eaan -E-Jung (1989), Ajooba (1991), Farz (2001), Kal Ho Na Ho (2003), Jab We Met (2007).\n\n
        He has received several film awards, some film awards are National Wrestling Alliance: Canadian Open Tag Team Champion,
        with Yukon Eric. Rustam-e-Hind (1954), Rustam-e-Punjab (1966).
        Wrestiling Observer Newsletter Hall of Fame - Class of 1996. He died on 12 July 2012 in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India.\n\n



    </string>
    <string name="haveli1">Haveli is a village in Shahkot in Jalandhar district of Punjab State, India.
        It is located 11 kilometres (6.8 mi) from Shahkot, 18 kilometres (11 mi) from Nakodar, 35 kilometres (22 mi) from district headquarter
        Jalandhar and 173 kilometres (107 mi) from state capital Chandigarh.
</string>
    <string name="wonderland1">A really nice place to hangout especially waterpark, the most important thing I like here is cleanliness
        and well mannered friendly staff.It is Located just 6 km from Jalandhar city bus station. The park offers complete fun package to people
        of all age groups, with several rides and attractions such as indoor dance club, slide splash, boating, bumper cars and hill queen train.
</string>
    <string name="science1">Pushpa Gujral Science City is located on Jalandhar - Kapurthala Road and spreads across a massive vicinity of 72 acres.
        It is named after Pushpa Gujral, mother of I.K.Gujral, one of India’s Prime Ministers. This science city project is one of the biggest science parks
        of its kind in North India. Science City was established with the aim of entertainment, excitement, learning, and amusement related with Science for people
        of all ages and groups.
</string>
    <string name="rock1"> The Rock Garden of Chandigarh is a sculpture garden in Chandigarh, India. It is also known as Nek Chand
        Rock Garden after its founder Nek Chand, a government official who started the garden secretly in his spare time in 1957.
        Today it is spread over an area of 40 acers.It is completely built of industrial and home waste and thrown-away items.
</string>
    <string name="tiger1"> Tiger Zoo in Ludhiana called as Tiger Safari ,situated 6 kms from the main city on GT Road on Ludhiana-Jalandhar Highway
        coveres an area of on 25 acres. It was established in 1993 and here one can see the majestic tigers are freely wandering in the dense forest,
        black bucks, sambhars, rabbits and lots of peacocks . It is a good picnic spot for the children and they thrilled to see the bathing of the tigers
        in the pool and sleeping under the bushe.
</string>
    <string name="stadium1">The Punjab Cricket Association IS Bindra Stadium is a cricket ground located in Mohali, near Chandigarh.
        It is popularly referred to as the Mohali Stadium. The stadium is home to the Punjab team. The construction of the stadium took around
        ₹ 25 crore and 3 years to complete. The stadium has an official capacity of 26,950 spectators.The stadium was designed by Arun Loomba and Associates,
        Panchkula and constructed by R.S. Construction Company, Chandigarh.
</string>
    <string name="ranjit1"> The Punjab Cricket Association IS Bindra Stadium is a cricket ground located in Mohali, near Chandigarh. It is popularly referred
        to as the Mohali Stadium. The stadium is home to the Punjab team. The construction of the stadium took around ₹ 25 crore and 3 years to complete.
        The stadium has an official capacity of 26,950 spectators.The stadium was designed by Arun Loomba and Associates, Panchkula and constructed by R.S.
        Construction Company, Chandigarh.
</string>
</resources>
